Let us have a discussion about the other files that was used for collecting the sense Q files
from the directory.
Okay.
The other application.
So one is which I have observed that was observance with.
So this is also one of a best tool to archive any data from the machine in a zbertar or
GC forming.
Okay.
So this is one of the file which we have absorbed a lot of times once if dot exe as well
as winter also absorb multiple times.
So this this tool is also one of the common application that that was used by other
detectors to collect the information from the collect the sense Q files from the machine.
Okay.
So I hope we are almost completed the collection section B because the collection section
will be only collecting the information like sense two files from the machine.
So you can see it here, are collected data, audio capture, browser section hijacking
something.
So we have seen this one and email collection will be also some of the time that attacks will
be collecting the email files from the machine.
So that is also one of scenario, video capture, screen capture, everything.
So I hope we are almost going to complete this and the next video will be the instant response
for the collection tactics.
pop off from here and we'll continue our discussion in the next video. See you guys! Bye!